嘿  丹  想要看看我们到目前为止开发的天气应用吗
Hey, Dan. want to see our weather app, so far, that we've been building?
看起来很棒  但我想看到更多的东西
>> Pretty cool. But I want something more.
嗯  我们还没有完成呢  我们才开始学习了2节课
>> Well, we're not done yet. We just started
让我们歇会  但是
two lessons ago. Give us a break. But fair
我们的确还有很多事情要做
enough, there's still a bunch more work left to
你认为我们下一步该做什么呢
do. What do you think we should do next?
对于初学者  让我们先做一个列表项
>> Well for starters, let's make the list
当我们点击时它时  它会做一些事情
item do something when you click on it.
好吧  你看起来是点击列表项的专家
>> Well, since you seem to be the expert on clicking on
为什么你不去做呢  我要去吃一些果冻豆
list items, why don't you do it? I'm going to go eat some jellybeans.
我认为Catherine刚才是在嘲弄我
>> I think Catherine was mocking me there.
说到"嘲弄"  让我们去做一些UI吧
Speaking of mocks, let's go do some UI.